这游戏怎么玩
So how does this game work?
Xbox360 Kinect运动: 第二季
就像手里真的有球那样扔出去吗
I just throw out like a real ball?
没错  就放轻松  往本垒投去
Yep. Just nice and easy, right over the plate.
好的
All right.
你个废物  沃罗威茨
You suck, Wolowitz!
你什么意思
What's that about?
起哄闹你啊
I'm heckling you.
这是棒球中很有爱的一部分
It's a beloved part of baseball.
他说得对
He's right.
而且估计你现在还在等着
And given that you're probably still waiting
被选进你五年级时那场球赛的队伍
to be picked for a game that was played in fifth grade,
我敢肯定你绝对废
I'm sure you do suck.
大家好  在干嘛啊
Hi. What's going on?
打棒球
Baseball.
我叫你们出去玩  指的可不是这样
Okay, this is not what I meant when I said go outside and play.
他在练习
He's practicing.
练来干嘛
For what?
天使队想找一个宇航员来当开球嘉宾
The Angels wanted an astronaut to throw out the first pitch,
美国职棒大联盟  洛杉矶安那罕天使队
主场位于加州橘郡的安那罕  也是迪士尼乐园所在地
所以你猜他们找了谁
so guess who they called?
什么  找你吗
What, you? Really?!
其他获邀的人都没空  于是就找我啦
Well, a lot of people who weren't available, but then me!
太酷了  恭喜你
That's so cool! Congratulations.
你现在算是你们小组里的运动健将了
I guess that makes you the athlete of the group.
不只他是好吗
Well, not just him!
我得提醒你一下  你正在跟
May I remind you that you're talking to the
找球手  击球手  追球手  与递水员说话好吗
seeker, beater, chaser and water boy
我们是第三名格里菲斯公园魁地奇队
of the third place Griffith Park Quidditch team.
我知道
I know.
看着自己男朋友鸡鸡下夹着一根扫把
Watching your boyfriend run around with a broomstick
这场面永生难忘好吗
between his legs isn't something you forget.
来吧  投一球试试
C'mon now, throw one.
好的  来吧
All right, here we go.
你看起来像个傻逼
You look like a jackass!
别闹了  你伤到人家的小心肝了
Cut it out! You're hurting my feelings!
现在你知道我们为什么不是在外面玩了
Now you know why we're not outside.
今天的讲课还喜欢吗
Did you enjoy my lecture?
不喜欢  我们的服务员也不喜欢
No, and neither did our waiter.
如果他们要卖康沃尔童子鸡
Well, if you're going to serve Cornish game hen,
就应该对康沃尔的历史了然于胸
you should either be familiar with the history of Cornwall
否则就得做好准备学习
or be prepared to learn it.
你这话的确很难反驳
It's hard to argue with that.
我懂是因为
And I know
我目睹一个只是撒胡椒的服务员
because I saw a sad man with a pepper mill
数次尝试  但都失败告终
desperately try and fail.
晚餐如何
Hey, how was dinner?
很棒  我吃了康沃尔童子鸡
Good, I had Cornish game hen.
可怜的服务员啊
Oh, that poor waiter.
谢尔顿  我们明天晚上去看个电影如何
Sheldon, how about tomorrow night we see a movie?
你们要连续两晚出去吗
You guys are going out two nights in a row?
我在火车之旅期间错过了数次约会之夜
I missed a number of date nights while I was on my train trip,
所以根据我们的恋爱合约
and I'm contractually obligated to make them up
我有义务把错过的夜晚补上
under the terms of the Relationship Agreement.
好热辣的恋情啊
That's so hot.
比热辣还辣  是契约"捆绑"
It's better than hot, it's binding.
如果你们明晚有空
If you're free tomorrow night,
我很乐意邀请你们来双重约会
I'd love to have you join us on a double date.
你知道双重约会不能抵两次约会的吧
You are aware that a double date doesn't count as two dates.
那你们爱来不来  我无所谓
Well, then come or don't. I don't care.
真不敢相信你腰酸背疼
I can't believe you're sore.
就连职业投手比赛完都需要有人按摩
Hey, even professional pitchers need a rubdown after the game.
但人家投的是真球
But they throw an actual ball.
你是往电视投空气
You were throwing air at a TV.
那我不得不提
For your information,
我还跟莱纳德来了一发超赞的击掌
I also gave Leonard one hell of a high five.
我有点惊讶你会答应
I'm kind of surprised you agreed to do this
在整个球场的人面前做这事
in front of a stadium full of people.
人家要办个太空日  而太空总署邀请我了
They're doing Space Day and NASA asked me.
我不好意思拒绝嘛
I felt like I couldn't say no.
好吧
Okay.
如果你需要  我可以帮忙你训练啊
Well, if you want, I could help you practice.
我成长期间打过不少垒球
I played a lot of softball growing up.
谢谢  这会很有帮助
Thank you, that would be great.
很好  那既然要做
Great. And while we're at it,
或许我们可以纠正你的跑步姿势
maybe we could butch up your run
好让你跑去投手丘时可以爷们点
for when you head out to the mound.
我的跑步姿势有啥问题
What's wrong with the way I run?
我就开个玩笑
Oh, just kidding.
当然没问题
Nothing.
谢尔顿  我有点惊讶你会选去酒吧
Sheldon, I'm surprised you'd choose to go to a pub.
在委员会会议时
At our committee meeting,
艾米发起了去公园野餐的提议
Amy made a motion for a picnic in a park,
我给这提议附加了一堆修正
but I tacked so many amendments on that thing
提议就像铅做的气球一样坠落了
it sank like a lead balloon.
所以我就提议去酒吧
I then suggested a pub.
我一开始心中也有诸多疑虑
Yeah, which I was initially skeptical of
直到我在网上看到他们有卖约克郡布丁
until I saw online that they serve Yorkshire pudding.
你都不喜欢吃约克郡布丁
You don't even like Yorkshire pudding.
是啊  恶心透了
No, it's yucky,
但是教导人们约克郡的历史
but informing people about the history of Yorkshire
那就是赞赞赞了
is yummy, yum-yum.
经过一场唇枪舌战
After a lively debate,
酒吧的提议以2比0的优势通过
that proposal passed by a two-zero margin.
真高兴看见两人这么忙碌
Nice to see a busy couple
还能坚持把官僚主义作风贯彻到底
keep the spark of bureaucracy alive.
无视他们  艾米  他们是嫉妒
Ignore them, Amy. They're just jealous
因为他们的感情永远不会像我们的这么好
because they'll never have a relationship as good as ours.
这时候他是不是要补一句"抖你玩"之类的
Isn't this when he says "bazooka" or something?
我不是在开玩笑
I wasn't making a joke,
我只是在陈述事实
I was merely stating fact.
我和艾米的感情比你们俩的好
Amy and I have a superior relationship to yours.
你不会真的这么认为  对吧
You don't honestly think that, do you?
对...莱纳德
Y... Leonard,
我还以为你知道呢
I assumed you knew.
从感情质量来看  我们这个圈子的
The ranking of relationships in our circle
排名顺序是  我和艾米
by quality is: me and Amy,
霍华德和伯纳黛特  拉杰和他女朋友
Howard and Bernadette, Raj and his girlfriend,
佩妮和夏敦埃酒  佩妮和你
Penny and Chardonnay, Penny and you.
根本不存在什么排名
There isn't any ranking.
就算有  我们也不可能垫底啊
And if there were, we wouldn't be at the bottom of it.
就是  而且我喝的是白苏维翁酒
Yeah, and actually, I drink Sauvignon Blanc.
所以你只对酒名错了有意见吗
That's the part you have a problem with?
安啦
Relax.
瞧  他们又吵起来了
There they go, fighting again.
你绝对不会听到她对白苏维翁酒这么说话
You'd never hear her talk that way to Sauvignon Blanc.
你小时候从未打过棒球吗
So you never played baseball as a kid,
连少年棒球联盟都没参加吗
not even Little League?
我本来要去的  但选拔赛那天
Well, I was going to, but the day of tryouts
我发现了我爸的《花花公子》系列藏书
I found my dad's Playboy collection.
我的手都累坏了
Threw my arm out.
职棒大联盟里投手丘的位置
All right, the pitcher's mound in Major League Baseball
应该是离本垒板60英尺又6英寸[18.4米]
is 60 feet, six inches away from home plate.
很好  你拿着这个
Great. You take this
够了就喊停
and say when to stop.
还有多远
How much further?
继续退
Keep going.
现在呢
How about now?
好了我会告诉你
I'll let you know.
你是喊停了吗
Are you saying "stop"
是不是我们太远听不见了
and we're just too far away to hear you?
好了  停
Okay, stop.
你这是在耍我吗
Are you kidding me?!
这距离就是60英尺
That's 60 feet.
60英尺不可能有这么远
There's no way this is 60 feet.
老娘看着卷尺的数呢
I'm looking at it.
你要明白现在不是我让你
You realize this isn't one of those times
故意夸大"某物"长度的时候
I want you to exaggerate how long something is.
好吧  我得...
Okay, I got to... I-I just...
我不得不问
I got to ask:
你凭什么认为你们的感情如此美妙
what makes you think that your relationship
而我们俩的却不是呢
is so wonderful and ours isn't?
首先
For starters,
我们享受在一起的时光
we enjoy spending time together.
我们也是
So do we.
我见过你们俩无视对方存在
And I've seen you guys ignore each other for hours
好几个小时  各忙各的
doing totally different things.
这叫"平行游戏"
It's called parallel play.
在同一场所玩相同的或者不同的玩具时
相互之间没有互动和交流
多半发生在3岁前的儿童之间
是啊  三岁小孩都这么玩
Yeah, toddlers do that.
不如我们玩得好
Not as well as we do.
那家伙真是有毛病  什么都要赢
You believe this guy? He has to be the best at everything.
那又怎样  你干嘛这么在乎
So what? Why do you even care?
你听他们的对话
Oh, listen to them.
这还没结婚呢  蜜月就已经结束了
Not even married and the honeymoon's over.
随你怎么说  你连去约会
Whatever. You can't even go on a date
都要三番四次核查你的《恋爱协议》
without checking your relationship agreement.
如果你对基于合同的关系有意见
If you've got a problem basing a relationship on a contract,
我想告诉你有13个有种的殖民地
I'd like to tell you about 13 plucky colonies
缔结了一份"关系协议"
that entered a "Relationship agreement"
又名美国宪法
called the U.S. Constitution.
但或许这么说不太好
And it may not be cool to say so,
但我认为直至今天  那份感情都还很火热呢
but I think that love affair is still pretty hot today.
还好我现在没穿着国旗图案的内裤
It's a good thing I'm not wearing flag underwear right now,
不然它会火热的烧起来
'cause there's about to be a fire.
其实没那么难
Okay, it's not that hard.
你只需看着你要投球的地方
You just look to where you want to throw it,
朝着那方向往前迈一步
step towards where you want to throw,
然后把球投出去
and throw it.
这就是你的建议吗
That's your help?
就好像在说"开飞机的步骤如下:
That's like saying, "Here's how you fly a plane:
首先上飞机
Get in the airplane,
知道目的地  然后开飞机"
know where you want to go and fly it."
先投球试试  看看你的实力
Just throw the ball. Let's see what we're working with.
加油  霍华德  燃烧你的小宇宙
Come on Howard, fire it in.
快给老娘投球
Throw the damn ball!
你们俩打算什么时候结婚
So when do you guys plan on getting married?
还不确定  但我想再等等
Uh, we're not sure. But I want to wait long enough
证明给我妈看  我不是带球结婚
to prove to my mother I'm not pregnant.
我可以吃一根你的薯条吗
May I have one of your fries?
当然可以
Of course.
我可以咬一口你的汉堡吗
Can I have a bite of your burger?
当然不可以
Absolutely not.
真是"完美"的一对
Some perfect couple.
他连食物都不愿意跟她分享
He won't even share his food with her.
汉堡有牛油果
It has avocado on it.
而她对牛油果过敏
She's allergic to avocado.
你嫉妒我和艾米到
Are you so jealous of our relationship
想她死这么严重吗
you want Amy to die?
我才没有嫉妒
I'm not jealous.
我只是觉得你把恋爱
I just think it's silly for you to compare relationships
拿来比较  就跟感情可以量化一样
like they're something that can be quantified.
任何事物都可以量化
Everything is quantifiable.
这炸薯条  7分
That French fry? A seven.
《蜘蛛侠》  9分
Spider-Man? A nine.
9这个数  奇怪的是只能得4分
The number nine-- oddly, only a four.
-这家伙有多奇怪啊  -百分百
- How ridiculous is he? - A hundred.
谢尔顿  你这只是按自己的喜好
Sheldon, you're just assigning random numbers
给东西乱打分罢了
to things based on your opinion.
才不是呢
No, I'm not.
炸薯条有三个变量
French fries have three variables--
松脆度  含盐量  形状
crispiness, saltiness and shape.
所以卷卷薯条只能得2分
Which is why a curly fry only gets a two.
如果想吃卷卷  我还不如点盘小丑的假发呢
If I wanted curls for dinner, I'd order a clown wig.
恋爱比炸薯条复杂多了
Well, a relationship is more complicated than a French fry.
贝尔伊德  施奈德和尾本的研究可不是这么说的
Not according to the work of Berscheid, Snyder and Omoto.
那三个流氓又说了什么
Oh, what did those rascals do now?
他们编写了恋爱亲密度问卷
They developed the Relationship Closeness Inventory,
用行为来预测恋人关系的稳定度
which predicts the stability of a couple based on behavior.
不要和炸薯条
Yeah, not to be confused
好坏问卷搞混了
with the French Fry Goodness Inventory.
那个是我库珀的大作
That's pure Cooper.
这问卷准确性高吗
So, this is accurate?
已经流行了25年
It's been around for 25 years,
也被其他研究者普遍证实有效
and has been extensively corroborated by other researchers.
这不会让恋爱有点不浪漫吗
Well, kind of takes the romance out of relationships.
有点  是完全不浪漫好吧
Kind of? It does it perfectly.
谢尔顿和我得了8.2分
Sheldon and I got an eight-point-two out of ten.
好  我们马上就做
Fine. We'll take it right now.
-别做  -怎么了
- No, don't. - What?
-别做就是了  -为什么啊
- Just don't take it. - Why not?
这太傻了  谁在乎得多少分呢
'Cause it's stupid. Who cares what number it is?
别这样  挺好玩的
Come on. It'll be fun.
我说了不让你做
I said I don't want you to.
我再去拿杯酒
I'm getting another drink.
抱歉
Sorry.
这次就算你两次约会吧
I'm gonna let you count this as two dates.
他们真是好累人啊
They're a lot of work.
觉得他有进步吗
Think he's getting any better?
有进步
Yup.
就差一点而已
That was a close one!
好的
Okay!
他不能推掉邀请了吗
Is it too late for him to cancel?
大概是吧
I think so.
小心啦  球来了
Heads up! Watch out!
你生气了吗
Are you mad at me?
别傻了  我没生气
No, stop being stupid.
我...松了口气
Um... whew?
你是气测试  还是气我们俩
Is this about the test, or is this about us?
我不需要通过测试
Look, I don't need a score on a test
让我担心原本就在担心的事情
to make me worry about something I'm already worried about.
你担心什么呢
What are you worried about?
我们订婚了  可我们没什么共同点
That we're engaged and have nothing in common,
这让我很害怕
and it scares me.
我也挺害怕的
Yeah, that scares me, too.
真的吗
It does?
有时候吧
Sometimes.
这可不是好事啊
Well, that's not good!
咱俩感情中坚固的基础
You being blindly infatuated with me was the rock
就是你盲目地迷恋我
we were building this relationship on!
那这么说会不会让你感觉好一点
Okay, well, this might make you feel better.
我俩都害怕婚姻会变成一场灾难
Uh, we're both scared that our marriage will be a disaster,
这就是我俩的共同点嘛
and so, that's something that we have in common.
而且  我俩都觉得我这人不好笑
Also, we both think I'm not funny.
看吧  你连笑都不笑
Huh? See, you're not laughing.
果麦圈客  你好啊
Hey, Froot Loops, what's up?
麦克  你好
Hey, Mike.
航天总局邀请我
Listen, NASA asked me to
为天使队开球
throw out the first pitch at an Angels game.
你能给我点建议吗
You got any advice?
可以  不要去
Yeah. Don't do it.
你还有什么事
What else you up to?
我为什么不能去呢
Why shouldn't I do it?
这事就没好处
There's no upside.
你开了好球  没人会在意
If you do well, no one cares.
如果你搞砸了
And if you screw up,
你的蠢态将在视频网站上千古流传
you're an idiot on YouTube forever.
可这是为了公益啊
But it's for a good cause.
都是为了全场看比赛的孩子们啊
What about all the kids that'll be there?
所以我才这么建议你
That's what I'm telling you.
小孩最贱了
Kids are the worst.
我亲生女儿上微博宣传我有个大鼻子
My own daughter tweeted I have a giant nose.
没准我投了个好球呢
Well, maybe I'll do a good job.
这可说不准
I don't know.
在太空里你连只笔都丢不过来
In space, you couldn't even toss me a pen,
那时候还是零重力呢
and that was in zero gravity.
谢谢你给我打气
Okay, thanks for the pep talk.
不客气  果麦圈客
Anytime, Froot Loops.
替我问候你的太太
Give your wife a hug for me.
她比你可爱一万倍
She's so much cuter than you,
都不知道你怎么泡到的
I don't know how you ever got her.
他人真好
He's so nice.
不好意思
Hey, sorry about that.
不  是我们不好意思
No, we're sorry.
我们一开始就不应该比较感情
We never should have been comparing relationships in the first place.
凭什么呀  我们赢了
Why? We won.
下次咱跟库萨帕里和他的狗约会吧
You know, I say, next, we take on Koothrappali and his dog.
给我们来点有难度的对手
Really give ourselves a challenge.
我只想多说一点
I just want to say one more thing about this.
佩妮和我是完全不同的人
Just because Penny and I are very different people
并不代表我们是差劲的情侣
does not mean that we're a bad couple.
一个简单测试便知答案
The answer is one simple test away.
就像那次我以为
You know, it's like when I thought
我的衣柜里有负鼠一样
there was a possum in my closet.
我只是袖手旁观怀疑吗
Did I sit around wondering?
不  我派莱纳德带着尖头棍和袋子一探究竟
No, I sent Leonard in with a pointy stick and a bag.
我杀了他的楚巴卡拖鞋
I killed his Chewbacca slippers.
我们接受测试
Let's just take the test.
不  我不想
No, no, no, I don't want to.
因为你知道我们的分数会很差
Oh, well, 'cause you know we're gonna do bad.
因为这根本不重要
Because it doesn't matter.
我不在乎我们得10分还是2分
I don't care if we're a ten or a two.
或1分  1分也是有可能的
Or a one. A one is possible.
婚姻令人害怕
Marriage is scary.
你害怕  我害怕
You're scared, I'm scared.
但这并没有令我不想结婚
But it doesn't make me not want to do it.
而是
It-it just...
令我想牵着你的手  与你一起步入婚姻殿堂
makes me want to hold your hand and do it with you.
莱纳德
Leonard...
如果你说这样的话  我会开心死的
It would make me so happy if you said things like that.
我们得了8.2分
We got an eight-point-two.
相信我  你已经开心死了
Trust me, you're happy.
我喜欢他们在中外场设计了瀑布
I love how they put a waterfall at center field.
令整个体育场浑然一体
It really ties the whole stadium together.
瞧你  居然在聊体育
Look at you, talking sports.
这真有意思对吗
This is fun, huh?
来看咱们朋友投出开场球
We get to see our friend throw out the first pitch,
吃个热狗  看看比赛
have a hot dog, watch the game.
没人说要看比赛啊
Nobody said anything about watching the game.
谢尔顿  那你以为会做什么
Sheldon, what did you expect?
我以为看霍华德投球
I expected to see Howard throw the baseball,
吃完热狗
finish my hot dog,
麻利地过街去迪士尼乐园
and hightail it across the street to Disneyland
正好赶上米奇的音乐大游行
just in time for Mickey's Soundsational Parade.
这样吧
I'll tell you what.
如果我们留下来  我就给你买棉花糖和摇头娃娃
If we stay, I'll buy you cotton candy and a bobblehead.
谁的摇头娃娃
Who's the bobblehead of?
有区别吗
Does it matter?
没有  只要摇头就行
No, as long as it bobbles.
华仔  我真为你骄傲
Howie, I am so proud of you.
谢谢  我也为自己骄傲
Thanks. I'm proud of me, too.
准备好了吗
You ready?
开始吧
Let's do it.
好的
All right.
祝我好运吧
Wish me luck.
加油
Go get 'em.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
天使体育场为致敬太空日
in honor of Space Day at Angel Stadium,
特邀请航天总局宇航员
the first pitch will be thrown out
霍华德・沃罗威茨投开场第一球
by NASA astronaut Howard Wolowitz.
谢谢大家
Thank you.
他真会投球吗
Can he really throw a ball?
-咱们魁地球队中他...  -那就是不行
- On our Quidditch team, he... - Yeah, that's a "No."
我要对今天在座的年轻人说几句
I have a message for the young people here today.
当我被邀请来开球时
When I was asked to throw the first pitch,
我脑袋里有个小声音说  "你不行"
a little voice in my head said I couldn't do it.
所以我反复练习
So, I practiced and practiced,
你们猜怎样
and you know what?
那个小声音
That little voice...
是正确的  但是
...was right, but...
我想起我不是运动员
...then I remembered that I'm not an athlete.
我是科学家
I'm a scientist.
所以今天的第一球
So, today's first pitch
将由科学直送本垒
will be delivered to home plate by science.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
孩子们  请看
boys and girls, I present to you
"火星漫游者"的工作原型机
a working prototype of the Mars Rover!
挥球转体
And here's the wind-up...
投吧
and the pitch!
为什么这么慢
Why is it going so slow?!
因为我是白痴  没考虑周全
'Cause I'm an idiot who didn't think this through!
火星车的最高速度为50毫米/秒  平均速度10毫米/秒
新计划
Okay, new plan.
我们去迪士尼乐园
We go to Disneyland,
在汤姆・索亚岛玩躲猫猫
play hide and seek on Tom Sawyer's Island,
然后回来看投球的结果
and then come back and see the end of the pitch.
我们等着球上本垒时
Okay, while we're waiting for the ball to arrive,
跟大家说说火星的有趣之处
here's some fun facts about Mars.
你个废物  沃罗威茨
You suck, Wolowitz!
他说得太对了
He makes a valid point!
得啦  再嘘也没办法速度变快
Okay, booing isn't gonna make it go any faster!